AKPOMUDIA SANDRA ABIODUN

NO 7, Komolafe Akanni street, Aduloju Ibadan.

+238160063880, | E-mail: icysandy96@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 26th December, 1996

Sex:. Female
Marital Status:. Single
State of Origin: Delta state
Local Government Area:. Ughelli North
Nationality: Nigerian

SYNOPSIS

A Higher National Diploma graduate of Computer Science who is self-motivated and committed to continuous improvement in work place through professionalism, experience and knowledge that will consistently achieve objectives. Efficient and able to work with less supervision.

EDUCATION

Federal Polytechnic, Ede.Osun StateHND Computer science2018-2020

Federal Polytechnic, Ede.Osun StateND Computer science2015-2017

City of Faith Comprehensive College, Ibadan Oyo State

O-Level School leaving Certificate 2008 - 2014

Sidehustle internship

(Customer Relationship Management) April 2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

NYSC

(Government school, ilorin) 2021 - 2022

ISON BPO

(AIRTEL customer care representative) October 2021

Abamcrest creation. 2019 - March 2020

(Cashier, replying of mails, calls to clients)

First City Monument Bank. (FCMB) 2017 - 2018

(Industrial Training)

Broadcasting corporation station (BCOS). 2016

(SIWES) (prepares program schedule,

assist in outdoor activities)

SKILLS

- Good Communication Skills.
- Ability to work with, and understand complex information.
- Ability to Write Good Report.
- Ability to Develop New Business and to Close Sales
- Customer Relationship Management Skills
- Good negotiation skills.
- Presentation Skills.
- Good accounting ability
- Ability to work without / less supervision
- Computer literate
- A good listener

INTEREST/HOBBIES

Researching, styling and making people happy.

REFERENCES:

MR. OYEWOLE AARON O. MD, IBEDC (Marketing Dept.) Ibadan 08055305141

MRS. FOLAKEMI JOHNSON CLINICAR AUTOMBILE, Ibadan 08030655447

MISS. VIVIAN ONOME JAMES SITE MANAGER, BAMBOO CONSTRUCTION LIMITED ABUJA 07068889605